《加州靡情》前情回顾
Previously on Californication...
我拿老婆的巧克力棒插清洁工的小穴
The miss's got me eating one of her chocolate bars
然后吃掉  结果被她抓到了
out of cleaning lady's vagina.
嗨  宝贝儿
Hello, darling.
你这操蛋的渣男
You fucking fuckface!
来认识这位诗人以及哲人
I'd like you to meet the poet and philosopher...
-老天  那是麦瑞林・曼森  -没错
- Oh Shit, it's Marilyn Manson - Marilyn Manson.
我们计划着搞个二重唱
We are talking about doing a duet together.
可能在国内巡演  这是件大事  对吧
Maybe tour of the States. It would be something, right?
我只是来吸粉的
I'm just here for the narcotics.
-我们准备结婚了  -朗克夫妇
- We're getting married !! - The Runkles!
我会在希腊剧院的舞台上主持婚礼
I'll fucking marry you fuckers on stage at the Greek!
太他妈赞成了
Fuck yeah, why not?
-你们也会来的  对吧  -什么
- You guys are coming on tour, right ? - What ?
我们得继续写这个音乐剧
We gotta keep writing this musical.
如果我们不在一起
If we are not together,
我也不会要你发什么独身誓言
I don't expect you to have taken some vow of celibacy.
凯伦  你要我不看别人就直接说出来
Karen, you want me to not see anybody else, just say the word.
我决定出国一段时间
I decided to go abroad, for an undetermined amount of time.
我要进行一场文学朝圣
I want to make a literary pilgrimage.
看着她离开  我不知道怎么说  就像
watching her go, I don't know.
就像一些事情已到尽头
It kinda feels like the end of something.
让你忍不住会想
Makes you wonder
她是不是我们还在一起的唯一理由
if she was the only thing that was still keeping us together.
你还争论个屁啊
How can you even debate this shit?
去吧  上路吧  别回头  你个傻缺
Go. Hit the road, don't look back, you fucking idiot.
-对  那如果...  -如果你妹啊
- Right, what if... - What if...
你这辈子就掉"如果"里了
You've lived your entire adult life according to "what if".
如果你想的那个人并不是你的真命天女呢
What if the one you think is "the one" Is not really "the one"?
你为何不闭上你的臭嘴再去给我到点酒呢
What if you shut your fucking piehole and pour me another drink?
你怎么想起来看我了
You came to see me.
对  但我也不知道我会梦到什么
Yeah, but I can't help where my dreams take me.
对  但你到那的时候梦到了什么
Yeah, but what do you dream about when you get there?
你的表情已经告诉我了
That says a lot.
那个傻妞是怎么回事
What the fuck is wrong with that ass?
没什么  她很赞
Nothing. She's pretty amazing.
某种程度上  她很适合我
In some way, she's perfect for me.
该来的总会来的  对吧
The eternal dilema, isn't it?
"家花"和"野花"之间的抉择
"Home, sweet home" Vs. "The wild cold world outside your door" .
你知道你的选择  你死都不后悔吗
You know which way you chosen. You'd die to regret it?
谁说的  我才不会这么说
Says who? It's not even me talking.
你懂的  我只是在问你问题
You know that. I just ask the questions.
你为什么这么怕放开她
Why are you so afraid to give up and let go?
没关系  汉克  我们试过但失败了
It's ok, Hank. We tried and we failed.
那不会是世界末日的
It's not the end of the world.
但我要是放弃了你  我还剩什么
But, if I gave up on us, what would I have left?
你的余生
The rest of your life.
汉克
Hank.
你没事吧
You OK?
梦遗了而已
Just a wet dream.
你怎么这么早就收拾行李了
Why on earth are you packing so early?
首先  现在是中午了
Well, first of all, it's noon.
第二  今晚演出结束后我还是会走的
And second, I'm still leaving after the show tonight
所以我们面临着一个实质性问题
which brings us to the real question,
我是否应该打包两份行李
should I be packing for two?
因为我非常确定
Cause I'm pretty sure
你的那些黑T恤和牛仔裤我都能穿
I can fit in a multitude of black T-shirts and jeans and...
或者你可以先说服我来一炮
or I could be possibly persuaded to come back to bed
然后再去收拾
and postpone packing,
快说服我  [要汉克去舔她下面]
Be more persuasive.
你现在是在推我的头吗
Are you pushing my head now?
-天呐  -就一点点想
- Oh my god! - Just a little bit.
《加州靡情》第6季第12集
我硬了
And... I'm hard!
我谢你  汉克
Thanks, Hanky.
让我检查下
Let me check..
你个骗子  最喜欢你这点了
You're a liar. And love you for it.
那可不行  抱歉  小淘气
That's hardly appropriate. Sorry, naughty smurf.
她还没结婚呢
She's not married yet.
你确定你要穿这身去吗
Are you sure you wanna go through with this?
那你为什么不试着说服她脱掉呢
Why are you trying to talk her out of it?
对啊  你为什么不试着说服我脱掉呢
Yeah, why you be trying to talk me out of it?
查理和玛茜・郎克尔简直就是
Charlie and Marcy Runkle are
弗瑞德和埃塞尔・梅尔兹
50年代电影《我爱露西》里的人物
现代版的弗瑞德和埃塞尔・梅尔兹啊
the Fred and Ethel Mertz of our time,
他们是一个整体
they belongs together.
没错  如果你不介意
That's right. If you'll excuse me,
埃塞尔要去补补妆了
Ethel has to make yellow while
好让露西和里基聊聊他俩的破事
Lucy and Ricky discuss their issues and what not.
我可能会和阿提库斯一起去
So I...I've the chance to go with Atticus on the road.
-然后呢  -然后我觉得可能...
- And? - And I thought maybe...
你会想跟我谈谈  我也不知道
you would wanna talk about it, talk, I don't know.
我不应该替你做决定
I shouldn't even factor into your decision.
但是你会的  你一直都这样
But you do, you always do.
汉克  你想要我怎么办
Well...Hank, what do you want me to do?
我是说  像"请留下"
I mean, "Oh, please, stay!"
"让我们白头偕老吧"这种话
"let's live happily ever after"
我说不出口  你是想得到我的许可吗
I can't do that. Do you want my permission?
我是说  你是大人了
I mean, you're a big boy.
无论如何  你都得自己拿主意
You're gonna make your own decision about it, anyways.
另外  我想你好像跟别人正打得火热呢
Besides, I tought you're in a relationship with someone.
也许那种非恋爱的恋爱关系
Maybe that's what's good for you then
对你也挺好
like non-relationship relationship,
因为你不知道如何把握
cause you have hard time functioning
一场传统的恋爱关系
within confines of a traditional one.
好吧  但我们之间可从没传统过啊
Well, it was never anything traditional about us.
你有咱女儿的消息吗
Have you heard from our literaly pilgrim?
Iphone里的一款图片分享应用
没有  只有她在图片分享上传的些照片
No, only what she puts up on Instagram.
图片分享是什么
What's Instagram?
你俩之间的破事儿搞定了吗
Ok, you guys working your shit out?
和好了吗
You back together?
我想没有  好吧  这么说吧
I guess not. Ok, here's the deal,
我和查理要结婚了  知道为什么吗
me and CW Rocks are going to do this thing. And do you know why?
不知道  为什么
No, why?
因为我们会很他妈幸福的
Because we're gonna be fucking happy.
-你知道为什么吗  -为什么
- And you know why? - Why?
因为这他妈比一直深陷痛苦要强多了
Because it's better than being fucking miserable all the time.
我们俩经历的这一切
This whole time we've been out here
就像是在中年危机的过山车上
it's been like a midlife crisis roller coaster ride.
但现在都他妈已经结束了
And it's fucking over now.
所以让我们都能白头偕老吧
So lets all just live happily ever after.
好吗  好吗  就这么决定了啊
Good? Good? It's settled?
很好
Good!
怎么了
What's going on?
阿提库斯不得不卖了飞机来支撑巡演
Atticus's had to sell the plane to fund the tour
而且唱片公司没提供往常他们都提供的赞助
and the record company ain't giving the kind of support they used to.
并不是因为他的疯子老婆
And no thanks to that nutjob missus of his,
他只是很缺钱
he's having some serious cash-flow problem.
我们要开大巴去巡演
We're back to touring by bus.
-那个黄毛怪呢  -在卧室
- Where is that fucking ginger? - He's in the bedroom.
他想跟一个知道
He wants to talk with someone who understands
心碎是什么感觉的人谈谈
what it's like to live with heartbreak
我跟他说我很经验的
I told him that, you know, I've got lots of experience,
但他说他不管  他只想和你聊聊
but no, he doesn't care, he wants to talk to you.
阿提库斯
Atticus!
我们的摇滚明星这是怎么了
What's up rock star?
我今晚演出不了  汉克
I can't play the gig tonight, Hank.
为什么呢
Why is that?
我今早上回了趟家
I went home this morning,
我跪着求娜塔莉回心转意
and got down on bended need, and asked Natalie to take me back.
丫却叫我滚蛋
and she told me to fuck off.
她跟我玩儿完了  她这么做也是可以理解的
She's really done with me, which is understandable given my behavior.
但是我从没试过在没有她的幸运之吻下
But I've never done and opening
完成整场演出
without a good luck kiss from her.
以前她总是会给我来一次
Back in the early day, she used to give me
全方位的口交  像蛋蛋之类的都会口到
this really comprehensive blow job, like balls and all, you know?
尽管  我会觉得很奇怪所以射不了
Though, I was usually too wired to come.
老兄  你的故事可真可爱
That's a cute story, buddy.
但恐怕你的演唱会还得继续
But I'm afraid the big rock-roll must go on.
但我都10多年没坐过大巴了
But I haven't been on the bus in well over 10 years.
太失我身份了
It's so embarrassingly bargain basement.
你开玩笑嘛  外面那辆车很漂亮啊
Are you kidding? That bus out there, that's beautiful. That bus.
-你真的喜欢吗  -是的  很喜欢
- Really, you like it? - Yes, I love it. It's bad ass.
-够拉风吗  -灰常拉轰
- It's cool? - It's so cool.
就像陆地上的飞机
It's like a land airplane.
又省油  又环保
It's gas friendly, eco-friendly
真应该给你颁个奥斯卡环保奖
You'll probably win and award for that shit.
-你怎么做到的  汉克  -做什么
- How do you do it, Hank? - Do what?
你爱的女人就在外面
The woman that you love is out there
而且你知道你不能挽回她
and you know you can't have her.
你每天早上都怎么起来的
How do you get up in the morning?
用酒呗
Booze is always helpful,
艺术也可以
so is the art.
我写的东西都是关于她的  所以
Everything I write is either for her, or about her, so
我和她在一起  即使在我的作品里
I'm with her, even when I'm not,
我们没有
in my writting.
真感人  汉克
That's very moving, Hank.
-别哭  -为什么
- Don't cry! - Why?
很不合适
It's unbecoming.
你说得这么感人  我为什么不能哭
You said something moving, why shouldn't I cry?
你身上那种澳洲人的坚韧品质呢
What about your aussie blockiness?
或者英国人那种喜怒不形于色的品质呢
or your British stiff upper lip. Whatever the fuck you are.
我觉得你应该跟我一起去  汉克
I think you should come on tour with me, Hank.
我感觉如果我们完成了
I feel like if we finish our master piece,
我们关于爱的摇滚音乐剧
our rock opera about love,
也许我们都可以从女人中解脱了
maybe we'll both end up with the girl.
我会考虑的
I'll think about it.
还有
In the meantime.
你是想摇滚呢还是漏鸟呢
Are you ready to rock out, or cock out?
我必须承认这真的很酷
I'll admit this is pretty cool.
就像每天都在迪斯尼乐园里样
It's like Disneyland every day.
是啊  就是少了那些踩着踏板车的胖子
Yeah. Without the morbidly obese running around in scooters.
就连时间概念都不一样
Even the concept of time is different.
这种演唱会一般都是在夏天开的
It's rock and roll fucking summer camp forever.
-有时候该改改了  对吧  -谁说的
- It's got to end at some point, doesn't it? - Says who?
最终还是要"落叶归根"的
All roads lead back home eventually.
听起来像首乡村音乐
Sounds like a country song.
你是费斯  对吧
Hey. You're Faith, right?
对  是我
Yeah, that's me.
我是文斯  谜团乐队的
I'm Vince, from Mysstery.
两个S那个  我们今晚打头阵
Two s's. We're opening the show tonight.
你好啊  两个S的谜团乐队的文斯
Well... Hey, Vince from Mistery with to s's.
-祝你好运  -谢谢
- Good luck up there. - Cool, thanks.
我想知道你是否愿意
I'm wondering if maybe
去我们的车上看看
you wanted to come around to hang on our bus.
上面写有"猫俱乐部"的那辆
It's the one that says "Cat Club"
之所以那么叫是因为每个想上来的小妞
We call it that because chicks who want to come on
都会被我们要求在前门的垃圾桶里尿尿
we ask them to pee on this litter box we keep by the front door.
这样我们就能知道她们是不是自愿来的
This way we know for sure that they're willing to party.
我无所谓啊  我尿泡里都满了
I'm free, I got a full bladder.
不过我想你还是不必来了
I don't think you'd have to do that, though,
因为你太出名了
because you're pretty famous.
谢谢你的热情邀请  但我不去  谢了
Thanks for the preferential treatment and all, no thanks
怎么  我们车容纳不下传说中的费斯吗
What? We're not big enough for the legendary Faith?
完全不是那样
No, it's not like that at all.
但你非要找茬的话
But if you're going to be a dick about it,
那我直说好了
I might as well come clean.
你们没那么有才
You're just not really that talented.
我听过你们的专辑
I've heard your album and,
跟商场里放的狗屁金属乐似的
it's really shitty mall metal.
换做是我的话就不折腾了
So, if I were you, I'd really just quit now,
说不定今年夏天你们还能在
and maybe Hot Topic will hire you back
Hot Topic是美国专注于
音乐  文化  服饰的连锁企业
Hot Topic上火一把
this summer.
你还挺贱的
Wow, you're kind of a bitch!
嘴放干净点  怎么跟女士说话呢
Hey, watch your manners, son. That's no way to talk to a lady.
滚开  老头
Fuck off, dad.
知道该怎么收拾他吗
You know what this calls for?
掐奶龙爪手
Titty twister!
晚上好  洛杉矶的朋友们
Good evening, Los Angeles!
你们想看最棒的演出吗
You wanted the best?
我可是一路堵车到这尼玛比弗利山庄的
Well I got stuck in the traffic coming on the fucking hill.
途经火星  来自英国伦敦
From London, England, by way of Mars.
Bacardi系列演唱会为您呈现
The Bacardi Concert series presents:
阿提克斯・尼玛・费彻
Atticus Fucking-Fetch!
好运  不过你也不需要
Good luck out there. Not that you need it.
你是摇滚明星
You're a fucking rock star.
*我是你爱的奴隶*
*I'm a slave to your motherfucking love.*
*可惜我却操了一个修女*
*It's a shame I've had a motherfucking nun.*
*我是你爱的奴隶*
*I'm a slave to your motherfucking love.*
*可惜我却操了一个修女*
*It's a shame I've had a motherfucking nun.*
*我不是你的婊子*
*I'm not one of your god-damn bitch【求校】*
*干你  向前一步  拿来*
*Fuck you and stand and fetch it.*
*向前一步  拿来*
*Step and fetch it.*
这跟修女的斋戒生活差别很大吧
A long way from church, eh?
这不废话吗
Are you kidding me?
*xxx与穷人*
*xxx and poor.*
*地上的床*
*Bed on the floor.*
*门前的战争*
*Wars at the door.*
*xxx与穷人*
*xxx and poor.*
*在烈火中摇滚*
*Rock between the fire.*
你这猥琐的臭光头
Do you, bald fucking wanker,
愿意娶这位性感的树桩妹【啥】
take this sexy little tree stump,
作为你毕生所爱吗
to be your immortal beloved?
当然愿意这么做
I most certainly do.
做
Do!
行了  而你这只跟我共享过
Right. And do you, delicious little spinner,
一段缠绵的滚床单史
with whom I have shared a sexual encounter,
能让我一直坚挺到人生巅峰的可人儿
which will sustain me well into my golden years,
愿意接受这位
take this...
满身臭汗的无毛猪头
sweaty hairless pinhead
作为你此生最后一位性伴侣吗
to be the very last sexual parter of you entire life?
我的天
Jesus!...
既然你这么说的话
Well, when you put it like that...
我们就这么干吧  干吧
Let's do it. I do it.
很好  咱继续
Good. Let's get on with it.
以北加利福尼亚Sun Kill Moon教会
By the power vested in me
赋予我的合法权利
by the Sun Kill Moon ministry of Northern California
我现在宣布，你们正式结为合法夫妻
I now pronounce you wife and early【哈？】man.
既然大家都来了  还有谁想要在这
Now, while we're here, does anyone else feel like getting wedded
美妙的洛杉矶之夜顺便结个婚
in this glorious, glorious LA evening?
有人吗
Anyone?
有吗
凯伦
Karen.
凯伦  与我携手
Karen, be with me.
与我这个傻瓜共度余生
Spend the rest of your life with this fool,
余生努力保证不让你后悔
the rest of his life making sure you don't regret it.
而我这个傻瓜会用
and this fool will spend
你看怎么样  宝贝儿
What do you say, babe?
-说愿意  -你愿意成为我的妻子吗
- Say Yes! - Will you be my wife?
快说愿意
Come on! Say yes!
没人想吗
No? Nobody?
真的吗
Really?
那就快滚下台去  全部消失
Then get the fuck off my stage. Be gone, all of you!
我写了下面这首歌献给我的妻子  娜塔莉
I wrote this next song for my wife, Natalie
希望她能原谅我
in hope that she'll forgive me,
就算她原谅了
although if she did,
也许我还会再次捅出篓子
I'll probably just bugger it up all over again.
但今晚我要为我的
But tonight I'm going to play it
朋友和伙伴  汉克・穆迪演奏
for my good friend and collaborator,
因为他也了解心碎的滋味
Hank Moody who knows a thing or two about heart break himself.
*我从窗户的倒影里看到你在哭泣*
*I saw you're weeping as you're reflected in the window.*
*风里的爱情*
*Love above wind.*
*在7点27分*
*Seven, twenty-seven.*
*俯瞰这些城市  门襟越来越小*
*Look down at the cities, doors are slowly growing tiny.*
*当夕阳把普通的厨房渲染成天堂*
*As the sunset turns house kitchen into heaven. *
*你转过头  我把你的头发别在耳后*
*You turn your face to me and I tug your hair behind your ears.*
*说一切都会安好*
*Say nothing can go wrong.*
*只要我们在一起*
*So as long as we are together.*
*So as long as we are.*
*只要*
*So long...*
*只要我们在一起*
*So as long as we are together.*
*So as long as we are.*
-等等  你看起来真眼熟  -汉克・穆迪
- Wait, you look familiar. - Hank Moody.
-别闹  -曼森
- Come on. - Manson.
感谢来给我的操蛋秀捧场
Thank you for coming to my fucking mother show.
Brian
Hi, Brian.
实际上  你来了我还挺意外
Actually, I'm surprised that you came.
有件事得澄清一下  之前是逗你玩的
I just want to make it clear, I was just fucking with you.
我没给你女儿毒品
I did not give drugs to your daughter.
因为我待会自己吸还不够呢
Because I need them for later.
那孩子还好吗
But wait. How is the kid?
-挺好的  -不错
- She's great. - Good.
能麻烦你让他把阿提克斯
Would you get her to send me
舔我蛋蛋的照片发给我吗
the picture of me tea-bagging Atticus?
-没问题  -因为我想发到脸书上
- Will do. - Because I want to put that on my Facebook.
成
Will do.
你俩要不是一对的话  我就会尿你屁股里
Okay, and if you guys aren't together I'd pee in your butt.
-啥  -麻烦把酒给我
- What?!  - Drink please.
是贝卡打来的
It's Becca.
-亲爱的  -嗨  老爸
- Hey sweetie. - Hi, dad.
这一路上怎么样
How's the road treating you?
这里美极了  老爸
It's so beautiful out here, dad.
我现在生活如鱼得水
I'm having the time of my life.
-明天就去欧洲了 -真为你高兴
- And tomorrow we leave for Europe. - Glad to hear it.
你开心吗  老爸
Are you happy, Dad?
这个问题太沉重了
Tha...tha--that's a loaded question.
我在思考我希望身边的人
I was just thinking about
都能得到些什么
what I want for all the people in my life.
结果我只想让你开心快乐
And I realized I just want you to be happy,
想看到你发自内心的微笑
I want to see you smile and know you mean it.
-你嗨了吧  -非常嗨
- Are you high right now? - Significantly.
我们抽了超赞的大麻
We just smoked some killer weed.
不出所料
Of course you did.
当心点  甜心
Be careful, sweetie.
玩尽兴  但也e嗨过头
And have fun, just not too much.
不用担心  老爸
Don't worry, dad.
条条都是回家的路
All roads lead back home.
感觉跟乡村歌曲似的
That sounds like a Country song.
我爱你  老爸
I love you, dad.
我也爱你  心肝儿
I love you too, sweetie.
帮我个忙提克斯舔曼森蛋蛋的
Would you do me a favor and send Mason
照片发给曼森吧
that photo of him tea-bagging Atticus.
行啊
Ok, will do.
好  爱你  亲爱的
Ok, sweetie, I love you.
我跟你一起去
I'm coming with you.
这下我可高兴了
That makes me so very happy.
*我是*
*Oh and I'm...*
*我是你甜蜜的负担*
*Is all the sweet misery*
*当你种下欲望之树*
*When you shape the tree of temptation.*
*当我*
*Oh when I...*
*我认识遗失在沮丧里的海滩上串脚印*
*I know the feet around the coast of paradise lost in frustration.*
*爱的火焰还在燃烧*
*And the flame still burns.*
*在我的灵魂里为未了的目标燃烧*
*It is there in my soul for the unfinished goal.*
*爱的火焰还在燃烧*
*And the flame still burns.*
挺好的  哥们儿  你做了正确的决定
Good for you, man. You made the right decision.
再说了  你要真有那胆
Besides, if you actually had the balls
跟她求婚  她也答应了
to do it, and she actually said yes,
你又会怎么做
what would you have done?
我会当场跟她结婚
I would've married her right there and then.
然后什么
And then, what?
你们先会跟兔子一样疯狂地干几天
You would have fucked like rabbits for a couple days,
说些腻味的枕边话
you would have had some sweet pillow talk,
接着某一天她就会
and then one day she would ask you
美国家得宝公司
全球最大的家居建材零售商
让你跟她一起去家得宝买东西
to go to Home Depot with her.
你就玩儿完了
Party is over.
你总高谈阔论游戏人生
You know, you talk a good game,
但你死的时候我在场
but I was with you when you died,
当时你正准备这么做
and you were about to do it.
准备最后一次放手追逐此生挚爱  伙计
You were gonna take one last shot at the love of your life, buddy.
是啊  我也许会尝试一下
Sure, I would have given it a try.
也许还能跟她滚床单
Maybe I could have gotten her in the sack again.
但最终  你起床后
But eventually, you get out of bed.
依然本性难移
You're still you.
一切的矛盾仍然在原地
All the problems you've ever had, they're still there.
所以就该放弃吗
So you're just supposed to give up?
不是放弃  而是放手
It's not about giving up. It's about letting go.
诚然接受自己
Finally accepting who you are.
猜猜是谁
Guess who.
老天  我恨不得她赶快死了下来陪我
God, I can't wait for her to die and come down.
凯伦
Karen?
Karen!
你要回去了  对吗
You have to go, don't you?
是的
Yeah, I do.
很抱歉  是的
I'm sorry, I do.
别道歉
Don't be.
你只是不知道自己会错过什么而已
You just don't know what you're going to be missing.
我知道
I do.
这正是分别如此艰难的原因
That's what makes it is so hard.
-我真的可以好好爱你  -费斯
- I could love you, you know. - Faith...
我不是说我现在爱你
I'm... I'm not saying that I do.
我是说将来可以
I'm saying that I could.
我很难动真情  所以有必要说出来
Which is rare for me, and deserves to be acknowledged.
你比任何一个我交往过的男人都理解我
You understand me, better than any guy I've ever been.
你懂我
You get me.
这种感觉最让人窝心
And that has been the nicest feeling.
我是说
I'm just saying.
我是说你非常了不起
And I'm just saying that you're pretty fucking amazing.
希望你能找到情投意合的那个他
I hope you find what you're looking for out here.
希望你能追回情投意合的那个她
I hope you find what you're looking for out back there.
我甚至会为你
I'll even say a prayer for you,
小小地祈祷一下
just not a very big one.
-讨厌跟你告别  -那就不要
- I hate saying goodbye to you. - Then don't.
知道吗
You know what?
从没真正在一起过的好处
The really great thing about never really being together:
就是永远不会分手
never really have to break up.
汉克  快走吧
Hank, get the fuck out of here.
否则我就要把你夹在双腿间让你留下
Before I wrap my legs around you and convince you to stay.
你知道这我不在话下
And you know I can do it.
怎么回事  擦
What is this? What fuck, wow?
-发生什么了  -汉克要走了
- What's going on? - Hank's got to go.
他要去追回旧爱【求校】
He's got to see a horse about a girl.
这是所谓追逐幸福吗
Is this about following your bliss?
跟昨天我们在床上说的那些有关吗
Is this about what we talked in bed yesterday?
-跟真爱有关吗  -是的
- Is it about love? - It is.
那你必须得走
Then you must go.
车不能为你调头
I can't turn the bus around,
但我能送你位幸福使者
but I cand send an emissary.
抱歉  又哭了
Sorry, crying again.
没关系  你哭得真难看
Don't be sorry. It's unbecoming.
好了  快走吧  我的任务完成了
All right, you. Go. My work here is done.
我知道你会一直幸福下去
I really see your happily ever after.
我知道他对你来说很重要
I know he means a great deal to you,
对我也是
as he does to me.
记住如果你需要的话  我会陪在你身旁
I just want you to know that I'm here for you, if you need me.
情感上
Emotionally,
精神上
spiritually,
很明显生理上
and obviously sexually.
谢了  阿提克斯
Thank you, Atticus.
我是认真的  亲爱的
I'm serious, darling.
有时性高潮可以缓解头痛
Sometimes and orgasm can relieve heartache.
我可是做过许多调研的
I've done a lot of research in the area.
至少来个好运之吻吧
Can I at least get a good luck kiss?
晚上还有演出呢
I've got a gig tonight, you know,
有点紧张呢
I'm a bit nervous.
我知道你不是个爱矫情的人  克鲁尔
I know you're not one for emoting, Krull,
但谢谢你
but thank you.
我曾经爱过一个女孩
I had a girl once,
曾以为是此生挚爱
love of my life she was.
结果当然还是弄砸了
Fuck it up, of course.
我以为我还有大把时间
I thought there'd be time.
却发现  我有的只是脚下的路
Turns out, it's just roads,
漫长又崎岖的路
long and paved potholes.
这是我在书里读到的
I read that once in a book.
去把她找回来吧  兄弟
Go and get her, pal